Guide to the Papers of Mordecai Sheftall (1735-1797), undated, 1761-1867, 1873, 1932, 1941 (bulk 1777-1778) *P-12
American Jewish Historical Society, Newton Centre, MA and New York, NY
- Subgroup II: American Revolutionary and Continental Troop Commissarial Work and Provision Return Records, undated, 1777-1779, 1782-1783
  - Series II: Commissarial Records - Army, undated, 1777-1778
    - Subseries XV: Provision Returns for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry, undated, 1777-1778
      - (Binder 10)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson, for Forty-nine Men of Different Troops Under the Command of Lt. Col. Marbury, 04/17/1778 (Item 29)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Thomas Claiborne for Forty-nine Men of Different Troops, 04/18/1778 (Item 30)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Fifty-eight Men of Different Troops Under the Command of Lt. Col. Marbur, 04/20/1778 (Item 31)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Thomas Claiborne for Joseph Faulks, 04/20/1778 (Item 32)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Thomas Claiborne for Rations to Henry Dinkins, 04/20/1778 (Item 33)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks for Rations to Henry Dinkins, 04/20/1778 (Item 34)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Samuel Scott, 04/20/1778-07/31/1778 (Item 35)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Twelve Privates Belonging to the Light Dragoons, 04/22/1778 (Item 36)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Different Troops of Lt. Col. Marbury's Company with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 04/23/1778 (Item 37)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Hardy Jenkins for Troops Belonging to the First Company of Light Dragoons, 04/24/1778-05/24/1778 (05/25/1778) (Item 38)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Lt. Col. Marbury's Company with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 04/24/1778 (Item 39)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Hardy Jenkins for the First Troop from 03/24/1778-04/04/1778, 04/28/1778 (Item 40)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Lt. Col. Marbury's Company with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 04/29/1778 (Item 41)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Adj. Walsh's Ration from 04/24/1778-04/30/1778 (Item 42)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Arthur Durley for Twenty-two Men, 05/?/1778 (Item 43)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Thomas Claiborne for Back Rations, 05/01/1778 (Item 44)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to George Bledsoe for Back Rations, 05/01/1778 (04/01/1778-05/01/1778) (Item 45)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Sheftall Sheftall to George Bledsoe Certifying Back Rations Due from 04/01/1778-05/01/1778 (Item 46)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Lt. Col. Marbury's Company with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 05/02/1778 (Item 47)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Joseph Culpeper from 03/10/1778-05/01/1778, 05/03/1778 (Item 48)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sargeant, Three Privates, One Woman, and One Child, 05/03/1778 (Item 49)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to John Pace for Back Rations from 03/10/1778-05/01/1778, 05/04/1778 (Item 50)
        - Provision Return [for the the Light Dragoons] Signed by John Grimké to Capt. Faulks for Thirty Men, 05/05/1778 (Item 51)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Arthur Durley for Two Men, 05/07/1778 (Item 52)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Nicholas Bryson for [Five] Men, 05/07/1778 (Item 53)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Henry Cannon for Twenty-one Men, 05/07/1778 (Item 54)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for a Part of the Light Dragoons, 05/08/1778 (Item 55)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Thomas Claiborne for Two Men, 05/08/1778 (Item 56)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Nicolas Bryson for One Man, 05/08/1778 (Item 57)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Henry Cannon for Seven Men, 05/09/1778 (Item 58)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks for Thirty-four Men of Capt. Faulks' Command, 05/11/1778 (Item 59)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by [Joseph Walsh] for Walsh's Rations, 05/11/1778 (Item 60)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Five Men, 05/12/1778 (Item 61)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert [Illegible] to Nicholas Bryson for Soap, Molasses, and Candles from 02/09/1778-05/13/1778 (Item 62)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Lt. Columb for His Rations, 05/13/1778-08/01/1778 (Item 63)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks to Nicolas Bryson for Rations, 05/13/1778-08/01/1778 (Item 64)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks for Sixty-five Men, 05/13/1778 (Item 65)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Three Men, One Woman, and One Child, 05/15/1778 (Item 66)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks with Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 05/16/1778-05/18/1778 (Item 67)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Arthur Durley for Two Men, 05/19/1778-05/20/1778 (Item 68)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Four Men, One Woman, and One Child, 05/19/1778 (Item 69)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks with Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 05/19/1778 (Item 70)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Arthur Durley for Three Men of the [?] Guard, 05/22/1778 (Item 71)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks with Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 05/22/1778 (Item 72)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sargeant, Two Privates, One Woman, and One Child, 05/22/1778 (Item 73)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks for One Lieutenant and Two Privates at Fort Howe, 05/22/1778 (Item 74)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks with Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 05/25/1778 (Item 75)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Three Men Under Capt. Faulks' Command at Fort Howe, 05/25/1778 (Item 76)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sargeant, Two Privates, One Woman, and One Child, 05/26/1778 (Item 77)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Capt. Faulks' Command with Numbers of Captain's Companies Provided for, 05/28/1778 (Item 78)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Fifty-three Men Under the Command of Samuel West at Reade's Bluff, 05/31/1778 (Item 79)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shem Cook of the Second Battalion for One Captain Doctor and Thirteen Men, 05/31/1778 (Item 80)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons of the 2nd Battalion Signed by Shem Cook for Thirteen Men, 06/01/1778 (Item 81)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Men, Women, and Children, 06/02/1778 (Item 82)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shem Cook for One Doctor and Thirteen Men, 06/02/1778 (Item 83)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Fifty-three Men, 06/03/1778 (Item 84)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shem Cook for Fifteen Men [Fragment], 06/03/1778 (Item 85)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by John Faulks for One Captain, One Doctor, and Fourteen Privates at Fort Howe, 06/05/1778 (Item 86)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Arthur Durley for One Lieutenant for a Single Ration, 06/05/1778 (Item 87)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Quarter Master, One Sargeant, and Eight Privates, 06/05/1778 (Item 88)
      - (Binder 4)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by William Johnson for Two Men Under the Command of Lt. Col. Harris, 06/06/1778 (Item 5 [089])
      - (Binder 10)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks for One Captain, One Doctor, and Four Privates, 06/06/1778 (Item 90)
        - Provision Return the Light Dragoons Signed by William Gilmour for Fifty-four Men, 06/06/1778 (Item 91)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by William Gilmour for Two Men Under the Command of Lt. Col. Harris, 06/07/1778 (Item 92)
        - Provision Return for the [Light Dragoons] Signed by Shadrack Wright for Samuel Scott, 06/08/1778 (Item 93)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for [Illegible], and Eight Privates, 06/08/1778 (Item 94)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Two Privates, One Woman, and One Child, 06/08/1778 (Item 95)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by William [Illegible] for Capt. [Illegible], 06/08/1778 (Item 96)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by William Gilmour for Fifty-six Men Under the Command of Lt. Col. Harris, 06/09/1778 (Item 97)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Fifty-three Men Under the Command of Lt. Col. Harris, 06/10/1778 (Item 98)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Four Privates, and One Woman, 06/12/1778 (Item 99)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Fifty-three Men Commanded by Lt. Col. Harris, 06/16/1778 (Item 100)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Sergeants, Three Privates, One Woman, and One Child, 06/15/1778 (Item 101)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Lee De Keyser and Leonard Marberry for Hardy Jenkins from 11/15/1777-01/07/1778, 06/16/1778 (Item 102)
        - Provision Return for the Light Infantry Signed by John Bard for Ten Men Under the Command of Lt. Col. Harris, 06/16/1778 (Item 103)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Four Privates, and One Woman, 06/16/1778 (Item 104)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Fifty-three Men Commanded by Lt. Col. Harris, 06/16/1778 (Item 105)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Nicholas Bryson for Forty Troops Under the Command of Lt. Col. [Harris], 06/17/1778 (Item 106)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Four Privates, One Woman, 06/19/1778 (Item 107)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott for Capt. [Illegible's] Command for [?] Sergeants, and Thirteen Privates, 06/19/1778 (Item 108)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for a Part of the Regiment, 06/19/1778 (Item 109)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott for the "3rd and 4th Regiment of Light Infantry", 06/19/1778 (Item 110)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott for the Light Infantry, 06/20/1778 (Item 111)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott for Seventy-five Men of the Light Infantry, 06/21/1778 (Item 112)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by John Bard with Numbers of Individual Regiments Provided for, 06/22/1778 (Item 113)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeants, Four Privates, and One Woman, 06/23/1778 (Item 114)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by John Bard for Those Commanded by [Lt.] Col. Harris with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 06/24/1778 (Item 115)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Hardy Jenkins for the First Company, 06/24/1778-07/24/1778 (Item 116)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Samuel Scott With Numbers of Persons Provided for, 06/26/1778 (Item 117)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Negro Belonging to Samuel Scott, 06/26/1778 (Item 118)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Five Privates, and One Woman, 06/26/1778 (Item 119)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Men, 06/26/1778 (Item 120)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry for the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd Battalions, 06/27/1778 (Item 121)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott for Forty-one men Commanded by Lt. Col. Harris for Rum, 06/29/1778 (Item 122)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragonns and Light Infantry Signed by Samuel Scott With Numbers of Persons Provided for, 06/29/1778 (Item 123)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Samuel Scott With Illegible Numbers of Persons Provided for, 06/29/1778-06/30/1778 (Item 124)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by John [?] for [?] Men [Fragment], 06/30/1778 (Item 125)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson and Samuel Scott with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/01/1778 (Item 126)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by James Scott for Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Under the Command of Lt. Col. Harris, 07/02/1778 (Item 127)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Samuel Scott With Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/02/1778 (Item 128)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson and Samuel Scott with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/03/1778 (Item 129)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Samuel Scott And Sergeant Campbell with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/03/1778 (Item 130)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott for One Man, 07/03/1778 (Item 131)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by John [Illegible] for One Sergeant, Seven Privates, and One Woman, 07/03/1778 (Item 132)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson and Samuel Scott with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/04?/1778 (Item 133)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson and Samuel Scott with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/06/1778 (Item 134)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson and Samuel Scott with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/07/1778 (Item 135)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott with Numbers of Persons for Companies Provided for, 07/07/1778 (Item 136)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Sergeants, Six Privates, One Woman, and One Child, 07/07/1778 (Item 137)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for [Illegible], 07/08/1778 (Item 138)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson and Samuel Scott with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/09/1778 (Item 139)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Hardy Jenkins for Rations Due to Jenkins from 05/24/1778-06/24/1778, 07/09/1778 (Item 140)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/10/1778 (Item 141)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Six Privates, and One Woman, 07/10/1778 (Item 142)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/11/1778 (Item 143)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons and Light Infantry Signed by Elijah Dickinson, with Numbers of Persons Provided for, 07/12/1778-07/13/1778 (Item 144)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Six Privates, and One Woman, 07/14/1778 (Item 145)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Jonathan Hunt for Back Rations, 07/15/1778-08/02/1778 (Item 146)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Man, 07/16/1778 (Item 147)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant and Two Privates, 07/17/1778 (Item 148)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Sergeants, Seven Privates, and One Woman, 07/17/1778 (Item 149)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Nicholas Bryson, 07/17/1778-07/31/1778 (Item 150)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by John Bennis for Five Men Under the Command of Lt. Col. Roberts, 07/20/1778 (Item 151)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Three Sergeants, Nine Privates, and One Woman, 07/21?/1778 (Item 152)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Four Men, 07/21/1778 (Item 153)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Walsh's Ration, 07/22/1778 (Item 154)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Four Men from 07/19/1778-07/22/1778 (Item 155)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for Two Sergeants and Twelve Privates, 07/23/1778 (Item 156)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Hardy Jenkins for First Dragoon Troop on Order of Lee De Keyser, 07/24/1778-08/24/1778 (Item 157)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks for Joseph Faulks, 07/24/1778-07/30/1778 (Item 158)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to Thomas Claiborne, 07/24/1778-07/28/1778 (Item 159)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to John Cater, 07/24/1778 (Item 160)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to William McDaniel, 07/24/1778-08/03/1778 (Item 161)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Hardy Jenkins from Sheftall Sheftall for Rations for [Hardy Jenkins] on Order of Lee De Keyser, 07/24/1778-08/24/1778 (09/18/1778) (Item 162)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks for Four Sergeants, Fifteen Privates and One Woman, 07/25/1778 (Item 163)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for [Isaac Middlebrooks?] and [John Hurley], 07/26/1778-07/29/1778 (Item 164)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Six Men, 07/27/1778 (Item 165)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Fifty-two Men, 07/29/1778 (Item 166)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Shadrack Wright for One Sergeant, Seven Privates and [Two] Women, 07/30/1778 (Item 167)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and [Illegible] for Six Men for Back Rations, 07/31/1778 (Item 168)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Fifty-two Men, 07/31/1778 (Item 169)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel Scott to Samuel Scott [Two Returns], 08/01/1778-10/01/1778 (Item 170)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson to John Connor, 08/01?/1778 (Item 171)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks for Lt. Gilmour, 08/02/1778-08/07/1778 (Item 172)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks for Lt. McDaniel, 08/02/1778-08/07/1778 (Item 173)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Henry Cannon from 07/21/1778-08/03/1778 (Item 174)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks to Sheftall Sheftall for Joseph Faulks Rations, 08/03/1778 (Item 175)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for One Man, 08/03/1778 (Item 176)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Sixty-one Men, 08/03/1778 (Item 177)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Robert Thompson, 08/03/1778 (Item 178)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks for Lt. [Bryson], 08/03/1778-08/10/1778 (Item 179)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Fifty-two Men, 08/05/1778 (Item 180)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks to William Mosley, Wagon Master to the Light Dragoons for Back Rations; Certified by Mordecai Sheftall, 08/06/1778 (04/12/1778-08/05/1778) (Item 181)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Sixty-two Men, 08/07/1778 (Item 182)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for [Robert Thompson], 08/07/1778 (Item 183)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks for Lt. Gilmour, 08/10/1778 (Item 184)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson and Joseph Faulks for Seventy-seven Men, 08/10/1778 (Item 185)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Joseph Faulks for Sixty-eight Men, 08/12/1778 (Item 186)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by James West to Sheftall Sheftall for Joseph Faulks, 08/14/1778 (Item 187)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Robert Thompson, 08/14/1778 (Item 188)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West and Robert Thompson for Sixty-two Men and One Woman, 08/14/1778 (Item 189)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Robert Thompson for Joseph Faulks, 08/15/1778-08/27/1778 (Item 190)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Thirty-seven Men, 08/17/1778 (Item 191)
        - Provision Return for the Light Dragoons Signed by Samuel West for Salt Provisions for Forty Men, 08/17/1778; WPA_D-0157; Indexed #076 (Item 192)